Guide to the Rice University Photograph Files, 1910-2015 UA 363
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
Rice University Photograph Files
1910-2015
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas https://library.rice.edu/woodson
Rice University
UA 363
23.6 Linear Feet
4.94 Gigabytes Nearline access: UA0363aip_001 (4.94 GB)
0.077 Gigabytes UA0363aip_002 (0.077 GB)
15.6 Gigabytes UA0363aip_003 (15.6 GB)
This collection includes individual files for photographs of Rice related persons, photographs of Rice University views, interiors, and buildings, photographs of Rice related events, and more. The contents are donated by Rice community members and/or gathered by the Woodson Research Staff, and represent one of the most heavily used portions of the University archives.
Biographical / Historical
This collection includes individual files for photographs of Rice related persons, photographs of Rice University views, interiors, and buildings, photographs of Rice related events, and more. The contents are donated by Rice community members and/or gathered by the Woodson Research Staff, and represent one of the most heavily used portions of the University archives.
Scope and Contents
This collection includes individual files for photographs of Rice related persons, photographs of Rice University views, interiors, and buildings, photographs of Rice related events, and more. The contents are donated by Rice community members and/or gathered by the Woodson Research Staff, and represent one of the most heavily used portions of the University archives.
Conditions Governing Access
This material is open for research. Stored on-site at the Woodson Research Center.
Index Terms
Subjects
Social life and customs; Universities and colleges; Sports
Document Types
photographs
Subjects (Corporations)
Rice University.; Rice University -- history.
- Series I: Individual photographs (Rice related individuals)
  - Abercrombie, Josephine
    General
    See: P-Group- Hackerman, Norman and Gene, James E. Lyon, Josephine Abercrombie; P-Group- Abercrombie, Josephine; P-Group- Hackerman, Norman and Abercrombie, Josephine
  - Abraham, Abraham
  - Abrahamsen, Roy F.
  - Adams, Charles Henry
  - Adams, John A.S.
  - Adair, Linda
  - Aguirre, Dr. Angel
  - Akers, William W.
    Related Materials
    See also: P-Group- Akers; Gallagher
  - Alborn, Ray
  - Aleala, Benito
  - Allen, Herbert
  - Allender, Laurel
  - Alsobroob, Margaret S. (Mrs. Dave)
  - Altamira y Crevea, Rafael
  - Altenburg, Edgar
  - Alumni - Single Shots
  - Anderson, Craig A.
  - Anderson, D.K.
  - Anderson, Ralph
  - Andrews, William Orus
  - Annis, Dr. Edward
  - Apple, Max
  - Arbogast, Todd
  - Arbuckle, Philip Heckman
  - Arnold, E.F.
  - Arnold, June Davis
  - Arnold, Oren
  - Ashcraft, F.W.
  - Atkinson, Vernon T.
  - Attwell, J. Evans
  - Auston, David
  - Autry, Allie May (Mrs. Edward W. Kelley)
  - Awapara, Jorge
  - Axson, Stockton
  - Bailar, Benjamin
  - Baird, F. Carroll
  - Baker, Donald Roy
  - Baker, James A. (Capt.)
    See also: P-Group Board
  - Baker, James A. (Judge)
  - Baker, James A. III
  - Baker, Stewart A.
  - Bale, Allen Melbert ("Red")
  - Ballew, William V. Jr.
  - [Mrs.] Barbie
  - Barker, J.R.
  - Barnard, Mary
  - Barnea, Amir
  - Barnes, Mary W.
  - Baron, Andy
  - Barrett, Deborah
  - Bartlett, Dr. Henry Leigh
    See Homecoming 1969
  - Baxter, Trevor
  - Beall, James Eric
  - Bearden, Frank
  - Beerman, Albert L.
  - Beissner, Henry M.
  - Belanger, Philip David
  - Bell, Robert L.
  - Berling, Grace Selma
  - Berman, Ronald
  - Berndt, Jerry
  - Bernhard, Jim
  - Berry, Dr. Michael J.
  - Bethea, Samuel Rice
  - Biddy, Scott
  - Bielawa, Sandra Soderlund
  - Bier, Charles A.
  - Birkhoff, George D.
  - Bixby, F. Lovell
  - Bixby, Mary
  - Blair, Dr. Lyman Curtis
  - Blair, Marvin S.
  - Blair, Mrs. Robert K. (Freeman, Madeline)
  - Blake, Norman B.
  - Blanchard, Thomas Frederic
  - Bland, Robert L.
  - Blanshard, Brand
  - Blau, Margaret
  - Blayney, Lindsay
  - Bloch, Felix
  - Blumenthal, Michael W.
  - Bobbitt, Jame F.
  - Bochner, Soloman
  - Bofill, Richard
  - Boles, John
  - Bonney, Roger
  - Boone, Cari
  - Boothe, Nancy
  - Borel, Emile
  - Boren, William H.
  - Boterf, Chester
  - Boulanger, Mlle Nadia
  - Bourgeois, Andre
  - Bourgoin, Sandra
  - Bourne, Henry Clark Jr.
  - Bowen, Harry Lee
  - Bowen, Ray M
  - Brady, David W.
  - Bransford, Dorothy Manning
  - Bray, Hubert Evelyn
  - Briant, Elizabeth
  - Briggs, Faye
  - Brochstein, Raymond
  - Brody, Dr. Baruch A.
  - Bronson, Bertrand
  - Brooks, Philip R.
  - Brotzen, Franz
  - Brown, George R.
  - Brown, Katherine Tsanoff
  - Brown, Lee P.
  - Brown, Peter
  - Brown, Watson
  - Broyles, William Dodson
  - Brunson, Emmett Evander
  - Bryan, A.B.
  - Bryant, R.L.
  - Bryson, Barbara White
  - Buccheri, Joseph R.
  - Buckley, Vincent H.
  - Budd, Ralph
  - Bulbrook, Harry M.
  - Burchfield, Burrell Clark
  - Burgess, Danny
  - Burns, John D.
  - Burrus, Charles Sidney
  - Bush, George
    See also: [James A. III] Baker Institute for Public Policy Groundbreaking (Preparations and Ceremony) 10/20/1994
  - Bushey, Mrs G.L.
  - Butcher, E.
    See also: P-Group- Hartsook, A. J.; E. Butcher
  - Butcher, Freeman L. ("Butch")
  - Butler, Marilyn Rae
  - Bultrick, Dr. George Arthur
  - Byrne, Tina
  - Cackowski, Jean Marie
  - Cadwallader, Oscar Julius Jr.
  - Cain, E.S.
  - Cain, Lester L.
  - Caldwell, Peter C.
  - Caldwell, Robert Granville
  - Camfield, William A.
  - Campbell, Philip III
  - Cargill, Jennifer
  - Carrington, Samuel M.
  - Carrion, Vincente
  - Carroll, F.R.
  - Carroll, Michael
  - Carson, Clarence Leon
  - Carter, E. Finley
  - Carter, [President] Jimmy
  - Castaneda, Dr. James A.
  - Caudill, William W.
  - Chance, Jane
  - Chandler, Asa Crawford
  - Chapman, Alan Jesse
  - Chappelear, Patsy S.
  - Chappell, R.H.
  - Chavanne, Harry
  - Cheatham, Dr. John B. Jr.
  - Chency, Walter Lynn
  - Chillman, Helen
  - Chillman, James Henry Jr.
  - Chrone, Robert E.
  - Clark, Howard Charles
    See also: P-Group- Clark, Dr. H. C.
  - Clarke, Ewell Albert Jr.
  - Class, Dr. Calvin M.
  - Clayton, Donald Delbert
  - Clayton, William
  - Cleary, Patricia Ann
  - Cline, Allyn
  - Cloutier, Paul A.
  - Coan, Bartlett E.
  - Coffie, John Byrd
  - Cohen, Agnes
  - Cohen, Robert
  - Coleman, Stewart P.
  - Coleman, William Beyer
  - Collier, Everett Dolton
  - Colston, Thomas M. Jr.
  - Comalander, Mark
  - Condon, Nancy Sue
  - Conklin, Edwin Grant
  - Conley, Patrick
  - Connor, William K.
  - Cook, Charles W.
  - Cook, St. Clare
  - Cookenboo, Leslie Jr.
  - Cooper, Joseph
    See also: P-Group- Cooper, Joseph
  - Cooper, Keith
  - Cooper, Paul
    See also: P-Group- Cooper, Paul and Shirley Trepel
  - Copeland, W.G.
  - Correll, Ross M.
  - Cosby, Bill
  - Couger, Quincy H.
    See also: Memorabilia- Cotton Bowl Pocket Watch
  - Coulter, Camille
  - Cox, Ed
  - Cox, John L.
  - Craig, Dr. Hardin Jr.
    See also: P-Group- Craig, Dr. and Mrs., 1991
  - Cram, Ralph Adams
  - Crane, Col. C.J.
  - Crawford, Bartholow Vincent
  - Crews, Jeff
  - Croce, Benedetto
  - Croneis, Carey
  - Crooker, John H.
  - Crottford, Carl
  - Crump, Caryn
  - Cummings, Robert Emmett
  - Cungus, Howell
    P-Group: Cungus, Howell, Class of 1930
  - Curl, Robert F.
  - Curtis, Morton L.
  - Curtis, R.W. "Bob"
  - Cuthbertson, Gilbert Morris
  - Cyert, Richard M.
  - Dain, James Warren
  - Daniell, Percy John
  - Dankworth, David C.
  - Darden, Bille Jo (Mrs. Billie Chappell)
  - Darling, Clarence Ransome Jr.
  - Datta, Evelyne
  - Davies, Joseph Ilott
    See also: P-Group- Huxley, Julian
  - Davis, Belinda
  - Davis, Bill
  - Davis, Edward
  - Davis, Joe
  - Davis, Malcolm E.
  - Davis, Margaret
  - Davis, Mark
  - Davis, Robert L.
  - Davis, Dr. Sam H. Jr.
  - Dawson, Clint
  - Dawson, Frank M.
  - Dawson, John Robert
  - de Menil, Dominque
  - de Vries, Hugo
  - Dean, Alice Crowell (Miss)
    See also: P-Group- Dean, Alice Crowell
  - Dean, Daphne
  - Deans, Harry Alexander
  - Denman, Arthur B.
  - Dennis, Dr. Herbert Knight
  - Dessler, Alexander J.
    See also: P-Group- Dessler, Dr. A. J. and Dr. Fred S. Keller
  - Devine, Carolyn
  - Dewitt, Mrs. Gayle
  - Diamant, Nicholas S.
  - Dix, Mary
  - Dix, William S.
  - Djou, S.K.
  - Dodge, H.T.
  - Doerr, John
  - Dore, John L.
  - Dormant, Julian Austin
  - Doty, James R.
  - Doty, Janice Cornell
  - Dowden, Dr. Wilfred S.
  - Drew, Dr. Katherine Fischer
    See also: P-Group- Hyman, Harold M and Katherine F. Drew
  - Driskill, Linda
  - DuCharme, Wesley M.
    See also: P-Group Prof. DuCharme
  - Dugat, Reginald Eugene
  - Duggan, Edmund Buchwalter
  - Duggan, Lee Jr.
  - Dunbar, Robyn
  - Duncan, Bob
  - Duncan, Charles W. Jr.
  - Dunn, Dorothy
  - Dupree, Edmund M.
  - Durrenberger, Joe A.
  - Dvorak, John Jerry
  - Eggert, Allen
  - Eggert, Katherine
  - Emison, Sam S.
  - Enders, Allen C.
  - Ensey, John
  - Erkel, Olive (Mrs. Leroy Bell)
  - Ernst, Eliot Dowman
  - Etnyre, Bruce
  - Eubanks, Thomas
  - Eudey, Garry
  - Evans, Griffith Conrad
  - Evans, John B.
  - Evans, Junius A.
  - Ewing, William Maurice
  - Falconer, Sir Robert
  - Farr, Louis L.
  - Farrell, Michele L.
  - Farren, Mrs. Paul
  - Faucher, Manuel
  - Fay, Homoiselle Haden
  - Ferguson, Gary Kent
  - Finer, Judith
  - Fitzpatrick, Colleen
  - Fitzpatrick, Thomas Kevin
  - Flowers, Kay
  - Fondren, Mrs. Walter W. Sr.
  - Fondren, Walter
  - Foote, Stephen A.
  - Ford, [President] Gerald
    See also: Events- Baker Institute Groundbreaking
  - Foston, Frederick
  - Fox, Mike
  - Frampton, Kenneth
  - Francis, Mrs. Addie M.
  - Francisco, George
  - Freeman, Charles
  - Freund, Friedrick Ernst Max
  - Fri, Robert
  - Friday, A. Randall
  - Frindell, Sander Berton
  - Fryer, Glenn T.
  - Fulwiler, Howard D.
  - Furlong, Randall C.
  - Gallagher, Dr.
    See also: P-Group Dr. Gallagher
  - Gallagher, Jerold C.
  - Gallegly, Joseph S.
  - Gammage, Earl W.
  - Gammage, T. Earnest Jr.
  - Gammill, Elbridge
  - Ganchan, Mildred
  - Ganchan, Richard Price
  - Gantt, Martin Benjamin Jr.
  - Garcia, Caroline
  - Garnett, Oliver R.
  - Garrison, Don
  - Gaylord, Thomas Keith
    See also: P-Group- Gaylord
  - Geiselman, Grover J
  - Gessler, Mark D.
  - Gilbert, Allan H.
  - Gillingham, James
  - Gillis, Don
  - Gillis, Malcolm
  - Gipson, Jackie
  - Glanville, James W.
  - Glascock, Clyde Chew
  - Glass, Graham P.
  - Glasscock, Susie
  - Glennan, Thomas Keith
  - Glidden, Bill
  - Godsey, Frank W. Jr.
  - Goodhue, Bertram Grosvernor
  - Gordon, Richard
  - Gordon, William E.
    See also: P-Group- Gordon, W. E.
  - Goss, Henry Frank, Jr.
  - Goyen, William
  - Gragg, Hugh
  - Gragg, Mrs. Hugh E. (Gans, Annette)
  - Graham, Wayne
  - Grandjean, Burke Dorn
  - Grawstein, WIlliam Caspar
  - Greaney, Thomas Joseph Jr.
  - Greanias, George
  - Green, Wilson Allen
  - Greenwood, Jim
  - Gripon, Lee Hardy
  - Grob, Alan
  - Grubbs, Mike
  - Gruber, Ira Dempsey
  - Guerard, Albert Leon
  - Guernsey, Frank
  - Guerrero, Elba
  - Guillory, Paul
  - Gwin, G.T.
  - Hackerman, Gene (Mrs. Norman)
  - Hackerman, Norman (2 folders)
  - Hackerman Unprocessed
  - Haden, Donald
  - Hagigi, Moshe
  - Hall, Arthur E.
  - Hall, Josiah A.
  - Hall, Robert P.
  - Hall, Walter G.
  - Hamill, Ray D.
  - Hamilton, Stephen E.
  - Hansen, Christian Andreas Jr.
  - Hanson, Jon Dean
  - Hanszen, Harry C.
  - Hardy, Joyce Pounds
  - Hargrove, James W.
  - Harman, G.S.
  - Harp, William Myers
  - Harris, Nell
  - Hartsfield, Robert J.
  - Hartsook, Arthur J.
    See also: P-Group- Brown, George and Prof. Hartsook
  - Harvard, Charles
  - Hasselman, Karl
  - Hatcher, Tilly
  - Hatchett, Terry
  - Hathorn, John Broadus
  - Hauge, Robert H.
  - Havens, Adrian Neil "Sandy"
    See also: P-Group- Haven, Neil "Sandy" and Drama Students
  - Haymes, Robert C.
  - Hayton, Ben C.
  - Healy, Bill
  - Heaps, Dr. Claude William
  - Heard, John Francis
  - Heinrich, Richard Lawrence
  - Heinze, Shirley Rowell
  - Heisman, John W.
  - Hellmuth, Nelson
  - Hellums, Jesse David
  - Hellums, Mrs. Bonnie Crane
  - Henry, Charles "Chuck"
  - Hermann, George H.
  - Herndon, Thomas B.
  - Herring, Robert
  - Herting, Edward W. Jr.
  - Heschel, Abraham Joshua
  - Hess, Jake
  - Hess, Wilbur
  - Heymann, Dzeter
  - Hicker, Doralyn
  - Hicks, Marion
  - Higginbotham, Sanford Wilson
  - Hightower, Joseph W.
  - Hill, Thomas
  - Hines, Greg
  - Hirasaki, George J.
  - Hirsch, Sam
  - Hirschey, Mark
  - Hjertberg, Coach Ernst "Ernie"
  - Hoagland, Ray Watkin
  - Hobby, Oveta Culp
  - Hobby, William "Bill"
  - Hoefer, H. Carl
  - Hole, Frank
  - Holland, John G.
  - Holliman, W. Cone
  - Holt, Edward C.
  - Honegger, Arthur
  - Hoover, R.B. "Buzz"
  - Hopkins, Mark
  - Hopkins, Thomas
  - Horn, Friedrich
  - Horton, Bonnie
  - Hosemann, Robert Paul
  - Houston, Sam
  - Houston, Wililam Vermillion
    See also: P-Group- Houston, W. V.
  - Howell, Ernest
  - Howell, John K.
    See also: P-Group- DuCharme
  - Howell, William
  - Howland, Ann
  - Huddle, Donald L.
  - Hudspeth, Chalmer M. (Hank)
  - Hudspeth, Demaris
  - Huff, Dr. Clay G.
  - Hugger, Fritz Franklin Jr.
  - Hughes, Arthur Llewelyn
  - Hulings, Doris Marie
  - Humphrey, Herbert Kay
  - Hunt, G. David
  - Huston, J. Dennis
  - Huston, Priscilla J.
  - Hutchison, Mary
  - Huxley, Sir Julian Sorell
  - Huxtable, Ada Louise
  - Hyman, Harold M.
  - Ibarra, Maria
  - Iglesias, Dr. John
  - Irwin, Keith
  - Isgren, Carl
  - Isle, Walter W.
  - Jacobs, Claire
  - Jennings, Ed. J.
  - Jennings, Ross
  - Jockusch, John S.
  - Johnson, Burnett H.
  - Johnson, Curtis O. Jr.
  - Johnson, Doug
  - Johnson, Francis Ellis
  - Johnson, Gaylord Jr.
  - Johnson, Lyndon B.
  - Johnston, Ted S.
  - Jones, Anita
  - Jones, Charles F.
  - Jones, Elizabeth
  - Jones, Henry (Sir)
  - Jones, Jesse
  - Jones, Robert
  - Jones, Samuel
  - Jones, Sidney L.
  - Joy, Dr. John
  - Kalb, E.F. "Tiny"
  - Karbalits, Olin Carroll Jr.
  - Katz, Larry
  - Keeler, Roger N.
  - Kehoe, Kim
  - Keller, Dr. Fred S.
  - Kelley, Edward W., Jr.
  - Kelley, Mrs. E.W. Jr. [Ellen Elizard]
  - Kemp, Lebbeus Courtright Jr.
  - Kennedy, John F.
  - Kennedy, Kenneth W. Jr.
  - Kidd, Albert N.
  - Kidd, Steve
  - Kiepper, Alan
  - Kikuchi, Baron Dairoku
  - Killgore, Doug
  - Kirk, Harris Elliott
  - Kitchell, James R.
  - Klindworth, Kenneth George
  - Klineberg, Stephen L.
  - Kloss, Bill
  - Knodel, Don
  - Kobayashi, Riki
  - Koch, Melton
  - Koderle, Elizabeth Jane Land
  - Kolenda, Konstantin
  - Konrad, Linn
  - Koonce, K. Terry
  - Lacey, Neal Terry Jr.
  - Landua, Kiel
  - Lane, Alvin H. Jr.
  - Lane, David
  - Lane, Dr. Neal F.
  - Lane, Sarah L. (Miss)
  - Lange, Hubert
  - Lanier, Cynthia
  - Larkens, Robert Pruett
  - Lassig, Oswald Joseph
  - Laux, Lila
  - Lay, Roy L.
  - Lear, Floyd Seyward
  - Lee, Eva
  - Leebron, David
  - Leeds, J. Venn Jr.
  - Leesemann, Charles Jules George
  - Leggett, Lloyd Waldo Jr.
  - Lehman, Lester O.
  - Lentricchia, Frank
  - Leray, Jean
  - Lethmayer, Erich
  - Letov, Alexander
  - Leung, Pui Lo
  - Levander, Caroline
  - Lewert, Dr. Robert M.
  - Lewis, Lendon E.
  - Ley, M/M Wendell
  - Lillard, James Gerard
  - Lingle, Roy P.
  - Lipscomb, Thomas G. II
  - Livingston
  - Loewenheim, Francis
  - Lombardi, Cesar
  - Long, Elizabeth
  - Love, Robert Marshall
  - Lovett, Edgar Odell
  - Lovett, [Mrs.] Edgar Odell
  - Lovett, H. Malcolm
  - Low, Frank J.
  - Lutes, Loren D.
  - Lyle, William Thomas
  - MacKail, John William
  - Maegle, Dick L.
  - Maer, Claude M. Jr.
  - Mailer, Norman
  - Malmberg, Charles Burton
  - Mandel, James P.
  - Manzo, Salvatore "Tony"
  - Marcus, George
  - Mardis, Jerlyn
  - Margrave, Dr. John L.
  - Marsh, Thad Norton
  - Marion, Leroy
  - Martin, Anne W.
  - Martin, William C.
  - Martino, Alfred
  - Martino, Anthony (Little Tony)
  - Martino, Salvatore (Tony)
  - Mascarenhas, Briance
  - Massingill, Jennings A.
  - Masterson, Harris III
  - Masterson, Dr. William H.
  - Mathias, Robert D.
  - Matusow, Allen J.
  - Mauldin, Charles R.
  - McCann, Samuel Glenn
  - McCants, Malcolm Thomas
  - McClane, John B.
  - McCleskey, Jerry
  - McCoin, Kenneth G.
  - McCool, W.D.
  - McCulley, John Howard
  - McEnany, Mike V.
  - McFarland, Emmett
  - McFarland, J.W.
  - McGinty, Milton
  - McIntire, Mary
  - McKillop, Dr. Alan Dugald
  - McKinney, David Bruce
  - McKinnon, Walter Lawrence "Dutch"
  - McKitrick, Thomas L.
  - McLemore, McCoy
  - McMurtry, Burt and Deedee
  - McMurtry, Larry
  - McNamee, Glenda
  - McNeeley, Holmes
  - McVey, Wililam M.
  - Mead, Margaret
  - Meredith, Paula
  - Meyer, Jacqueline Virginia
  - Meyerson, Albert
  - Michael, Dr. F. Curtis
  - Miele, Dr. Angelo
  - Miers, Sir Henry
  - Miller, Clarence
  - Miller, Hugh
  - Miller, James P.
  - Miller, Robert Floyd
  - Miller, Shelby
  - Milligan, Winfred Oliver
  - Millington, John W.
  - Mills, Miss Nellie
  - Mitchell, Ewell E.
  - Mitchell, O. Jack
  - Mitchner, James
  - Moffett, Tom
  - Montgomery, Lowell B.
  - Moody, Alvin
  - Moody, Dan
  - Moore, Charles C. Jr.
  - Moore, Charlie
  - Moore, Harvin Cooper
  - Moore, Harvin C., Jr.
  - Moore, Mary Louise (1931)
  - Moraud, Marcel
  - Morgan, Alpha
  - Morin, Robert B.
  - Morris, Harold
  - Morris, Henry Madison
  - Morris, Seth Irwin
  - Much, Kathleen
  - Muir, Andrew Forest
  - Muller, Herman J.
  - Murphy, Evelyn S.
  - Murphy, Walter D.
  - Mustaccia, James N.
  - Neely, Jess Claiborne
  - Nelson. H. Joe III
  - Nettleton, Lewis L.
  - Neuhaus, Max
  - Nevins, Allan
  - Newbigin, Leslie Rt. Rev.
  - Newman, James H.
  - Newmark, Nathan M.
  - Newport, John P.
  - Nicholas, Dr. Henry O.
  - Nicholson, Patrick James
  - Nicks, Marjorie Evelyn
  - Nielsen, Dr. Niels
  - Nordin, Obert L.
  - Nowlin, James Foster Jr.
  - O'Keefe, Richard L.
  - Olan, Levi (Rabbi)
  - Oliver, Covey
  - Oliver, Eugene Jr.
  - O'Neill, Haylett Jr.
  - Opalka, Roman
  - Orman, Ben F.
  - O'Rourke, Cathleen
  - Ostwald, Wilhelm
  - Paddock, Rita
  - Paget, R.T., Q.C., M.P.
  - Parish, Dr. John Edward
  - Parker, Robert Franklin
  - Parrish, General Noel
  - Parsons, David Goode
  - Patrick, Albert T.
  - Patten, Bob
  - Pattie, Frank Acklen Jr.
  - Pearson, David A.
  - Peden, Alexander Phillips
  - Peerman, Frank
  - Peet, Nicholas Peter
  - Penn, M.T.
  - Penrose, Roger
  - Perelman, Mel
  - Perkins, Sallie Shepherd
  - Perry, John S.
  - Perryman, Butler
  - Perzynska, Kinga
  - Peterson, J.R.
  - Peyre, Henri Maurice
  - Pfeiffer, Dr. Paul Edwin
  - Phelan, Rose
  - Phillips, Dr. Gerald C.
  - Phillips, Roland W.
  - Picton, Julia Nance
  - Pierce, George
  - Pitman, Russell
  - Pitzer, Dr. Kenneth Sanborn
  - Pitzer, Mrs. Kenneth Sanborn
  - Poincare, Henri
  - Polking, John
  - Pollak, Joe Luck
  - Pollard, Jack
  - Pomenoy, Patrician Jeanne
  - Pomerat, Roland
  - Pomertantz, James
  - Pound, Joseph Horace
  - Preble, Margaret Brisbine
  - Prehn, Walter Lawrence Jr.
  - Prelog, Vladmir
  - Price, Arthur Roy
  - Putzke, Roberta
  - Quaidy, Linda
  - Quillen, Carol
  - Quinby, John Rodney
  - Raaphorst, Madeleine R.
  - Rabson, Dr.
  - Rabson, Tom
  - Ragsdale, James A.
  - Ramer, David
  - Ramsey, William (Sir)
  - Randlett, Edward Atkinson
  - Raphael, Emanuel
  - Rath, Dr. R. John
  - Ravel, Maurice
  - Rawson, William Branton
  - Rayzor, J. Newton
  - Reeves, John Lloyd
  - Reichle, Alfred Douglas
  - Reid, John Lyon
  - Reilly, Joseph Frances Jr.
  - Reinke, Edwin Eustace
  - Reuis, Shirley
  - Reynolds, Fisher
  - Rhein, Walter Joseph
  - Rhoden, Don
  - Rhodes, Harold
  - Rhodes Scholarship candidates
  - Rice, David
  - Rice, Elizabeth Baldwin (Mrs. William M. Rice)
  - Rice, Homer
  - Rice, Wililam Marsh
  - Rice, Mrs. William Marsh (Bremond, Margaret C.)
  - Rice, William Marsh Jr.
  - Richards, Gwyn
  - Richardson, A.S.
  - Richardson, Elbeth Vesta
  - Richardson, James Thomas
  - Richardson, Sid W.
  - Richter, George Holmes
  - Riddle, Walter
  - Riemann, Wentworth Arnold
  - Rimlinger, Dr. Gaston V.
  - Risser, J.R.
  - Robertson, Bob
  - Robinson, Eldred Jay
  - Rodell, Elizabeth
  - Rodriguez, David
  - Rogers, Jimmy
  - Rogers, Karen Hess
  - Rooke, David Lee
  - Roos, Charles F.
  - Rorschach, Dr. Harold E. Jr.
  - Rosenberg, Yale Leonard
  - Rosenstein, Harris
  - Ross, David III
  - Roth, Bert
  - Rudisill, H. Clifford
  - Rumbel, Ketih E.
  - Rupp, George Erik
  - Russell, Dr. Paul F.
  - Ryan, Cornelius O.
  - Ryon, Lewis Babcock
  - Ryon, Lewis Babcock Jr.
  - [M.] Saint Hubert
  - Saldich, Robert J.
  - Salsburg, Zevi Walter
  - Samfield, Edwin
  - Sammy the Owl (Rice Mascot)
  - Samuelson, Patricia
  - Sass, Dr. Ronald L.
  - Savage, Catherine
  - Savoie, R.C.
  - Scheps, Clarence
  - Scherer, Dan
  - Schill, Gus A.
  - Schiller, James Curtiss
  - Scholars and Fellows
  - Schroepfer, Dr. George J. Jr.
  - Schuberth, Richard
  - Schum, David
  - Schwartz, Samuel Kent
  - Scott, Hugh
  - Scott, John Thaddeus
  - Scott, Marc
  - Seaborg, Glenn Theodore
  - Seller, Dr. James
  - Sewall, Blanch Harding
  - Shannon, Claude E.
  - Shaper, Steve
  - Shapiro, Beth
  - Shatto, Gloria McDermith
  - Sheid, Mark
  - Shelton, Jack
    Biographical / Historical
    During his career as a trainer at the Rice Institute, Jack Shelton was known as "Nigger Jack" to many. African Americans were specifically excluded from attending Rice under the original charter until it was broken in the early 1960's.
  - Shelton, Robert
  - Shields, David
  - Shipley, Dr. Arthur Everett
  - Sibley, Marilyn McAdams
  - Siegal, Cliff
  - Sihvonen, Oli
  - Simpson, James H. Jr.
  - Sims, Dr. James R.
  - Skaaren, Warren
  - Smith, A. Frank
  - Smith, Elizabeth
  - Smith, Dr. Gordon W.
  - Smith, Katrina
  - Smith, Marion Judson
  - Smith, Dr. Richard J.
  - Smith, Richard N.
  - Smith, Robert Calhoun
  - Smouse, Robert James
  - Snow, Shirley
  - Soligo, Ronald
  - Song, F.A.
  - Soule, Gardner
  - Spears, Dr. Monroe K.
  - Spence, Dale
  - Speer, James B.
  - Sperry, Rev. Willard L.
  - Spiegelman, Sol
  - Sproule, Jean Acheson
  - Stabell, Richard N.
  - Stafford, Ralph Donald
  - Stamey, Roderick A. Jr.
  - Stancliff, Fred J.
  - Standish, William M.
  - Stark, Paulina
  - Stauber, Dr. Leslie A.
  - Stebbings, Dr. Ronald F.
  - Stein, Gertrude
  - Stein, Robert
  - Sterling, Robert
  - Stormer, Carl
  - Strange, Ray Watkin Hoagland
  - Stratford, Mary Jane (Torrens)
  - Stratford, Mrs. Sara Pleasants (Mrs. W.R.J.)
  - Strauss, Lewis L.
  - Strauss, Louis
  - Streetman, Sarah Marie
  - Stremmel, Frances
  - [Freshman] Student between classes
  - Students - Girls Dorm Room
  - Student - Women's Cadet Corps - 1918?
  - Studney, Henry "Hank" Joseph
  - Suitts, Tommy
  - Sullivan, Louis W.
  - Sundt, Peter Christian
  - Swanson, Ben
  - Sylvester, John W.
  - Szent, Gyorgi Albert
  - Talbot, Raymond J. Jr.
  - Taliaferro, Dr. William H.
  - Talley, Robert Earl
  - Tallichet, Mary Estelle
  - Tapia, Richard
  - Taylor, Bill
  - Taylor, Sir Geoffrey
  - Taylor, William L.
  - Teague, James U.
  - Ten Brink, Doris M.
  - Ten Brink, Karl Cornelius
  - Thibedeaux, Murphy H.
  - Thomas, Everett Rue
  - Thomas, Tracy Y.
  - Thompson, Scott
  - Thomson, Sir George Paget
  - Thrall, Dr. Robert M.
  - Tidden, John Clark
  - Tittel, Frank
  - Todd, Prof. Anderson
  - Topazio, Dr. Virgil W.
  - Torczon, Linda
  - Tour, Jim
  - Toynbee, Arnold Joseph
  - Tsanoff, Radoslav Andrea
  - Tucker, John Garland
  - Tucker, Temple
  - Tuggle, Francis D.
  - Tully, Edward Aubry
  - Turnbull, E. Pender
  - Turner, Anna Lay
  - Turner, B. Bynum
  - Turpin, Jack Allan
  - Turrentine, Gordon Henry
  - Turrentine, Robert Emmett "Bob" Jr.
  - Tuttle, Phil
  - Tyler, Mike
  - Uher, Vincent
  - Ulrich, Floyd
  - Unger, Guinn
  - Vale, Wylie Walker
  - Van Court, Frant
  - Van Dusen, Mr. and Mrs. G.T.
  - Van Helden, Albert
  - Van Sicklen, William J.
  - Vandiver, Frank Everson
  - Vardi, Moshe